http://www.lehmans.com/privacy

Your Privacy Rights
Welcome to the Lehman's Online Store. We appreciate the trust you place in Lehman's, and we are committed to respecting your privacy and the security of your personal information. Lehman's strives to abide by the privacy practice guidelines and recommendations promulgated by institutions such as the Better Business Bureau (BBB) and Direct Marketers Association (DMA). We want to make you feel as comfortable shopping here as you would from our catalog or retail store.
Our privacy policy, updated on April 23rd, 2015, describes the information we collect and how we use it. It applies to the Lehman's website and all related sites, services, and tools where this policy is referenced.
We always welcome your questions and feedback. For privacy-related issues, please contact us at:
Lehman's, 289 N Kurzen Road, Dalton, OH, 44618
Phone from US: 800-438-5346
Phone from outside US: (Access Code) + 330-828-8828
Fax 330-828-8270
Email: info@lehmans.com
Contents
Information We Collect
Using Information We Collect
Information We Collect
We may collect information (including name, address, telephone number, email address, transaction information, credit card information and date of birth) when you:
Place an order from our catalogs or on our Web site
Make a purchase at one of our stores
Return an item or make an exchange
Inquire about our services
Request a catalog
Receive a gift package
Create an account at lehmans.com
Request a shipping quote
Post a review on our website
Comment on our blog
Create a wishlist or fill a shopping cart online or in our stores
Sign up for Lehman's email updates
Enter a contest or sweepstakes
Are referred to us through a marketing promotion
Participate in a marketing survey, promotion or event
Interact with us through Twitter, Pinterest and Facebook or other social media that share user information with us as governed by their respective privacy policies
Maintain a Lehman's charge account
Become a member of a Lehman's loyalty or rewards program
We maintain the data that you provide us, along with a record of your purchases, in a secure database. To best serve you, we may combine this information with data that is publicly available and data that we receive from other reputable sources. Please visit this link if you would like to opt-out of having your lehmans.com activity collected.
We also gather information about how visitors navigate through our Web site by using clickstream data gathered with "cookies" and other online tools such as "pixel tags." See Cookies and Pixel Tags for further information.
return to top
Using Information We Collect
At Lehman's, we always want to provide you with the best possible shopping experience and fulfill your orders exactly as you've requested. To do this, we collect information that allows us to:
Process and track your order
Provide the services you request
Contact you about the status of an order
Send you catalogs or promotional offers we believe will be of interest to you
Send you email updates and offers
Identify your product and service preferences
Customize our communications to you
Provide information concerning product recalls or products you have purchased
Improve our merchandise selection and customer service
return to top
Information We Share with Others and Your Privacy Rights
We contract with other companies to provide certain services, including shipping, name and address verification, email distribution, catalog distribution, live online chat, market research, third party advertising, promotions management and payment processing. We provide these companies with only the information they need to perform their services and work closely with them to ensure that your privacy is respected and protected. These companies are prohibited by contract from using this information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with anyone other than Lehman's.
Lehman's may employ third party sites and services that may be framed or masked (placing their website within a Lehman's website) to provide a pleasurable experience of shopping on Lehman's website or to provide important services. If Lehman's utilizes this capability, we exercise care in selecting the external website and review their privacy polices periodically.
From time to time, we make our mailing list (names and addresses only) and general shopping activity available to reputable companies whose products or services we believe will be of interest to you. We do not share email addresses for this purpose. If you do not want to receive mailings from other reputable companies and prefer that we do not share any information with these companies, please contact us
On rare occasions, we may disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, or when required by law to do so. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.
Our company and our trustedthird parties may share with one another anonymous versions of user informationcollected at this site. We may use that information to link to and issueanonymous cookies containing demographic or intent-based data for online behavioraladvertising purposes.  Such cookies do not contain personally identifiableinformation.  If you would like to opt out of online behavioraladvertising, click on one of these links:
http://www.aboutads.info/choices or http://networkadvertising.org/choices
return to top
Your Choices about Communication from Lehman's
We offer choices about the types of information you receive from us. If you prefer not to receive catalogs or email updates from Lehman's or if you prefer to receive them less frequently, please visit the Your Account section of www.Lehmans.com or contact us at the address shown above. You can also unsubscribe from our email updates using the link provided in each edition of the email.
If you do not wish to receive other communications from us, such as surveys, please contact us at any of the places mentioned above.
So that we can be sure to identify you correctly, please be sure to provide us your exact name and address, or the mailing label from your catalog. Because mailings are planned in advance, it may take several weeks for your request to become effective. If due to human error you continue to receive unwanted communications, please contact us again, and we will make every effort to correct the situation.
return to top
Third Party Catalog Opt-Out Services
Over the past several years, many third party services have become available to help consumers opt-out of catalog mailings. We currently do not honor requests made through these services, with the exception of Catalog Choice. We made this decision after careful consideration of customer service, data protection, privacy and whether or not fees were associated with the service. It is important to us that consumers not have to pay to make a catalog opt-out request. Catalog Choice met all of our requirements. If you prefer to use their service, we welcome you to visit their Web Site at catalogchoice.org. Whether you use Catalog Choice or contact us directly with your mailing preferences, we are committed to meeting your needs.
return to top
Cookies and Pixel Tags
A cookie is a small data file stored by your Web browser on your computer. Cookies enable you to place an order on our Web site. They also allow us to enhance and personalize your online shopping experience, so the information you receive is more relevant to you.
For example, we use cookies to:
Remember what items are in your shopping cart
Recognize you when you return to our Web site
Enables faster checkout, if you have created an account at lehmans.com
Study how our customers navigate through our Web site and which products they request in site searches
Deliver personalized marketing from Lehman's
If you set your browser to refuse cookies, please call us at 800-438-5346 to place your order.
We may also use pixel tags - tiny graphic images - to tell us what parts of our Web site you have visited or to measure the effectiveness of any searches you may do on our site. Pixel tags also enable us to send you email in a format you can read and let us know when you have opened an email message from us.
We may also contract with other companies who use cookies or other online tools such as pixel tags or Javascript to support the performance of a marketing effort on our behalf. We prohibit these companies from using this information for their own marketing purposes.  This information is used by Lehman's to share relevant marketing offers with you.
We also contract with third party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. To do this, they will collect anonymous information about your visits to our Web site and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other Web sites to target advertisements. These targeted advertisements may appear on other sites that you visit. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a cookie or pixel tag - industry standard technology used by most major Web sites. No personally identifiable information is collected in this process. These companies operate independently from Lehman's and have established their own privacy and security policies. To opt-out of this type of messaging, please contact us at any of the locations listed above.
return to top
How We Use Email
When you provide us your email address, we will email you as necessary to process your order, respond to a request or provide customer service. For example, after you place an order at lehmans.com, you may receive an email confirmation and, in most cases, an email with package tracking information. Recipients of gifts may also receive email notifying them of the gift and providing information about the gift.
We may also send promotional emails about products, special offers, services or events we believe may be of interest to you. It is our intent to send promotional emails only to those who wish to receive them. We provide instructions on how to unsubscribe in each email and you can also contact us at any of the locations listed above.
return to top
Links to Other Sites
Occasionally we provide links on our Web site to other sites to enhance the functionality and shopping experience. These sites operate independently of Lehman's and have established their own privacy and security policies. For the best online experience, we strongly encourage you to review these policies at any site you visit.
return to top
Updating or Reviewing Your Information
To update your customer information (name, address, telephone number and email address), please contact us at the address above. A limited amount of purchase information may also be available to you. To protect your privacy, we will need to validate your identity before you update or review your information.
return to top
Security
It is our intent to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you or received from a partner. We use a variety of current technologies and processes for protection of our customer data. We limit the information we provide to outside companies with whom we contract to only what they need to carry out their responsibilities. It is our practice to use encryption whenever we receive or transmit sensitive data.
Users can recognize a secure environment by the padlock symbol and the https://www.lehmans.com in the address bar. Lehman's utilizes both GeoTrust and DigiCert to encrypt the information being passed between the user's browser and Lehman's web server. Lehman's also provides a link to our encryption information by clicking on the GeoTrust seal in the footer of every page or clicking here.
return to top
Privacy of Children on Our Web Site
Our Web site is not intended for use by children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.
return to top
Policy Changes
From time to time, we may use customer information for unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change, we will post these changes on our Web site. Posted changes take effect immediately. We encourage you to review our privacy policy periodically.
return to top
Identity Resolution Privacy Policy Updates
Required Language:
"We also engage a third-party partner for the purpose of identifying users and delivering to them marketing on our behalf (i.e. email or direct mail). Our partners may collect information directly from your device, such as your IP address, device ID, and information about your browser or operating system; may combine personal and non-personal information about you with information from other sources; and may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. This activity enables them to identify you to facilitate the delivery of marketing on our behalf. To opt out of recognition services, please go here. To opt out of third-party cookies, please go here.
Questions or Comments?
For questions, comments or assistance, we invite you to contact us at any of the locations listed above.
We hope to answer any questions to your satisfaction, but should you ever want to contact a third party regarding our privacy practices, you can email the Direct Marketing Association's Committee on Ethical Business Practices at ethics@the-dma.org. The DMA is the oldest and largest association for consumers and companies with interest in direct marketing.
return to top
X
This site tracks visits anonymously using cookies. Close this dialog to confirm you are happy with that, or learn more in our privacy policy.
Agree and Close
Newsletter
Sign up for our email newsletter
Connect Online
In the Smithsonian
» Learn More
Categories
»
Farm, Garden & Tool
»
Health & Wellness
»
Home & Décor
»
Kitchen & Food
»
Lamps & Lighting
»
Stoves
»
Appliances
»
Toys, Books & Games
»
New
Lehman's Locations
» Visit Our Flagship Store - Kidron, OH
» View Our Store Events - Family Fun Events Every Weekend!
For a Simpler Life
»
Satisfying
»
Understandable
»
Sustainable
»
Preparedness
»
Comforting
Join Our Team
»
Careers
Have an Idea for a Product?You could win $100!
Get our catalogWant a catalog mailed to you?
Click here!
Our GuaranteeWe stand behind our products and want to make sure you are pleased.
Copyright © 1995-2020 Lehman Hardware and Appliances Inc, All Rights Reserved. Designated trademarks are the property of their respective owners.
Welcome to Lehman's, For a Simpler Life. If you are an American with a disability we offer a toll free disability services phone line at 800-438-5346 during regular business hours and one of our knowledgeable customer service representatives will help you navigate through our website, conduct advanced searches, read you the specifications of any item and consult with you about the products we carry. There is no charge for this assistance for any person with a disability calling from within the United States or Canada. Finally our customer service representatives will explain our privacy policy and terms of service and take your order if you so desire.
